Contact

dhruvarakesh20@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/dhruva-rakesh (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Cloud Computing Linux

Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Dhruva Rakesh

Student at IACSD Pune

Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

Summary

I am a recent graduate of the Vellore Institute of Technology, where I specialized in software development. He has experience in developing software applications using Qt Creator and Linux-based systems. I am is passionate about playing football, cricket, and swimming.

Experience

Institute for Advanced Computing and Software Development (IACSD)

Graduate Student

March 2024 - Present (2 months)

Pune, Maharashtra, India

Currently Pursuing my Post Graduate Diploma in Big Data Analytics (PG-DBDA) from Institute for Advanced Computing and Software Development (IACSD) at Akurdi, Pune.

VIT-AP

Student

July 2019 - June 2023 (4 years)

Amaravati, Andhra Pradesh, India

Indira Gandhi Centre for Atomic Research (IGCAR), Kalpakkam Project Intern

November 2022 - April 2023 (6 months)

Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

Education

Vellore Institute of Technology

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Electrical, Electronics and Communications Engineering (2019 - 2023)